{
    "question": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Which universe crossover was introduced in the &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic issue #247?",
            "correct_answer": "Mega Man",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Super Mario Brothers",
                "Alex Kidd",
                "Super Monkey Ball"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What&#039;s the race of Invincible&#039;s father?",
            "correct_answer": "Viltrumite",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kryptonian",
                "Kree",
                "Irken"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Which one of these superhero teams appears in the Invincible comics?",
            "correct_answer": "Guardians of the Globe",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Avengers",
                "Justice League",
                "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In Black Hammer, what city did the heroes save from the Anti-God?",
            "correct_answer": "Spiral City",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mega-City One",
                "Rockwood",
                "Star City"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "This Marvel superhero is often called &quot;The man without fear&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "Daredevil",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Thor",
                "Wolverine",
                "Hulk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In &quot;Homestuck&quot; what is Dave Strider&#039;s guardian?",
            "correct_answer": "Bro",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Becquerel",
                "Doc Scratch",
                "Halley"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "The main six year old protagonist in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what theologian?",
            "correct_answer": "John Calvin",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Calvin Klein",
                "Calvin Coolidge",
                "Phillip Calvin McGraw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Who is Batman?",
            "correct_answer": "Bruce Wayne",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Clark Kent",
                "Barry Allen",
                "Tony Stark"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "When was Marvel Comics founded?",
            "correct_answer": "1939",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1932",
                "1951",
                "1936"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What is the full first name of the babysitter in Calvin and Hobbes?",
            "correct_answer": "Rosalyn",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Rose",
                "Ruby",
                "Rachel"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "According to their longtime nickname, what kind of &quot;duo&quot; are Batman &amp; Robin?",
            "correct_answer": "Dynamic",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Dangerous",
                "Dynastic",
                "Delirious"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In &quot;Homestuck&quot; the &quot;Kingdom of Darkness&quot; is also known as?",
            "correct_answer": "Derse",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Skaia",
                "Prospit",
                "The Medium"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What is the alter-ego of the DC comics character &quot;Superman&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Clark Kent",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bruce Wayne",
                "Arthur Curry",
                "John Jones"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Who is the creator of the comic series &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Robert Kirkman",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Stan Lee",
                "Malcolm Wheeler-Nicholson",
                "Robert Crumb"
            ]
        }
    ]
}